americanewscentral.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy - American News Central

This Privacy Policy was created to help you understand how we collect, safeguard and use information that you provide to us.

By using our site, you represent that you are not under 13 years of age. You can visit this website (“Site”) without giving us any information about yourself. There are times when we may need to obtain personal information from you in order to provide certain services that you may request.

You can access the Site and browse some areas of the Site without disclosing any personally identifiable information. The Site’s web server automatically tracks basic information about visitors, including but not limited to IP addresses, browser details and referring pages. None of this information can be used to personally identify specific visitors. If you voluntarily chose to receive certain services, including but not limited to our Newsletter, Breaking News Alerts, Product Giveaways, Product Updates and Community Forum, we collect your personal information, including but not limited to your name, cell phone number, e-mail address and demographic data. This data is collected only when you choose to voluntarily provide to us such information by registering. Once you register at the Site or chose to receive certain services, you may no longer be anonymous to us.

If you would like to “opt out” of interest-based advertising delivered by advertisers on web pages using cookies, you may “opt out” by following the instructions available at [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed).

We use industry-accepted technology to protect your data from disclosure to unauthorized third parties. We collect, retain, and use personal data for the following purposes and services:

Contacting the User: We use your e-mail address, mail address, first name, last name and zip/postal code to contact you. Personal information is only used for legitimate business purposes, including corresponding with you regarding our site or services and to inform you of developments in our company or with our services that we believe may be of interest to you. Personal information is used to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, and to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Site, our users, and others.

Mailing List or Newsletter: We may also the information we collect, including but not limited to your name and zip/postal code, in order to occasionally e-mail you regarding important functionality changes to the Site or to e-mail you announcements and promotions related to our business, products, services or affiliate or partner organizations.

By using this Site, you consent to our collection and use of personal information you choose to provide to us. We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update this statement, and any such modifications, alterations, or updates will be effective upon posting.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

This Privacy Policy is revised as of May 10, 2015 and may be modified from time to time.
